http://www.arcadetown.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to iWin. IWin operates various websites with game-related products and services (our "Sites") and provides applications for the
provision of various online and mobile services, such as search and gaming (collectively, "Applications") through which personal information may be
collected. This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") applies to all personal information collected by iWin through our Sites and Applications.
If iWin is operating the Sites or Applications under an agreement with a specific partner, the branding of the Site or the Application will indicate the
specific partner with which iWin operates the Site or Application ("Identified Partners"). In such an event, iWin may share the data collected with that
particular identified Partner. Accordingly, iWin's use of your data is subject to our Privacy Policy - and our Identified Partner's use of your data is
subject to its privacy policy. You should familiarize yourself with such Identified Partner's privacy policy. Some of iWin's Identified Partners serve
their own ads or use other ad-serving networks. To opt out of data collection by an Identified Partner's ad-serving network, please see that Identified
Partner's privacy policy.
This Privacy Policy describes our practices regarding the information collected online through Sites and Applications maintained by iWin, and not to
websites or services offered and operated by other companies or organizations to which we link. Additionally, this Privacy Policy does not cover
information that we collect through other methods, such as mail-in sweepstakes.
IWin is headquartered in the United States and the collected data is stored in the United States. Although we operate Sites and maintain some operations
outside the United States, when you become a member of one of our online communities or programs, make a purchase from iWin or register for one of the
Applications, your account is with a United States company and your data will be stored in the United States. By registering and using this Site, Members
acknowledge that the processing of their personally identifying information for the purposes described above may involve the transfer of such personally
identifying information from within the European Economic Area ("EEA") to countries outside the EEA whose data protection regulation may not be as
stringent as that within the European Union.
In accordance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), this Privacy Policy contains information about the personal and usage data iWin
collects about each user, and how that information is collected, stored and managed.
To request your personal and product usage data, please email support@iwin.com.
BY USING THIS SITE, APPLICATION, OR USING ANY OF THE RELATED SERVICES, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ASSENT TO IWIN'S PRIVACY POLICY AND YOUR UNDERSTANDING THAT IWIN MAY
PROCESS YOUR DATA IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE FOREGOING, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE OR APPLICATION OR IF ALREADY A
MEMBER YOU MUST TERMINATE YOUR ACCOUNT.
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
If you are a visitor to a Site or a user of an Application, you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly provide us
with on an individual basis ("Personal Information") and statistical and usage information collected using cookies and other technologies as you browse the
Site or use an Application ("Usage Information").
1. Personal Information
Registration Information
You will need to provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your preferences when you register on one of the Sites or for one of the
Applications. The specific information collected will vary depending on the Site or Application, includes your email address and/or username (or player
name), . Registration is not required to browse any of our Sites, but you will not be able to view certain content or use aspects of certain Sites or
Applications that require registration if you do not provide the requested information.
Credit Card Information
If you choose to purchase products or services from us or our partners, you will need to provide a valid credit card number, postal code, expiration date,
and Security Code (CVV), in addition to email address and billing address iWin securely transmits Credit Card Information to our payment processor for
verification and processing, and never stores your full credit card number, expiration date or Security Code For subscription purchases, iWin stores the
last 4 digits of your credit card number, used for account, billing and purchase verification, and displays this in your secure Account page on the iWin
website and in the iWin Games Manager application For all transactions, iWin employs secure servers and the secure server software (SSL) to encrypt all
payment information. In all instances, iWin has made a substantial investment in server, database, backup, and firewall technologies to protect the assets
of the Site, including the confidentiality of information collected about Members. These technologies are deployed as part of a sophisticated security
architecture and protocol.
Email Information
In addition to providing us with your email address as part of registration, if you choose to correspond with us via email or by using a web interface to
reach customer support, we may retain the content of your messages together with your email address and our responses.
2. Usage Information
Similar to other commercial websites, we utilize standard technologies such as "cookies," clear GIFs (also known as "web beacons" or "action tags") and web
server logs to collect information about how the Sites and Applications are used. Additionally, when you connect to or download an Application, we may
retrieve information from the computer used to log onto the Application. The information we collect may include technical information about your computer,
system and application software, and peripherals, and any data related to the use and operation of the software used in connection with the
Application.
Cookies
As an important and necessary part of providing customizable and personalized services to our Members, iWin sites or its advertisers may use cookies, web
beacons, and similar technologies to store and sometimes track non-personal information about Members while on the Website. A cookie is a small amount of
data that is sent to a Member's browser from a Web server and stored on a Member's computer hard drive. Areas of iWin sites where Members are prompted to
log in or that are customizable require acceptance of cookies. These technologies are also used to help iWin track the response to messages sent to Members
on the part of marketers so that iWin can monitor and report campaign results to the marketer and track response history and campaign effectiveness. In
addition, banner advertisements are displayed on our websites which may contain certain cookies. While iWin uses cookies in other parts of our websites,
the cookies received with banner ads are collected by our advertising partners, and iWin does not have access to this information. Members may opt out of
the advertising that they see on our sites targeted specifically to them by going to the respective sites' privacy policy(ies) and following directions. To
opt out of Google's "interest-based ads" and to learn more about Google's collection of personal information to serve ads in connection with iWin, please
go to www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/. With respect to cookies, users have a choice. By modifying their browser preferences, they have the choice to
accept all cookies; they will be unable to use those iWin services that require the use of cookies in order to participate.
Clear GIFs
Clear GIFs are small, invisible graphic images (usually only one pixel) placed on a web page or email message to capture statistical usage information. They
are not used to collect personal information about you.
IP Addresses
An IP address is a number assigned to your computer every time you are connected to the internet. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server
as part of demographic and profile data known as "traffic data" so that appropriate data (such as the web pages you request) and geographically relevant
content can be sent to you.
HARDWARE ID
iWin stores the hardware id, a unique identifier associated with the PC computer you use to access our websites and Applications, to determine a unique user
within our systems. The hardware ID allows iWin to determine if multiple accounts have been created on the same PC, and to prevent attempts by a single
user or household to receive introductory offers to our subscription program(s) multiple times by using different email addresses or credit cards during
registration and checkout. multiple accounts or using multiple credit cards.
The hardware ID may also be associated with any activity the user has taken in the context of a marketing campaign, such as viewed a promotional page,
installed the Download Games Manager Application, initiated a game download, created an account or created a subscription, or canceled the a
subscription.
CUSTOMER ID
When a user creates an account on the iWin system, that user is assigned a Customer ID, which is displayed in the Personal Information section of My
Account. The Customer ID gives the user a fixed non changing identifier that stays with their account from point of creation.
When a user registers on the iWin system, a single sign on account is created, and a unique user identity (uuid) is generated at this point in time and
saved in the user’s database record. This uuid does not change over time, unlike other personal data such as email address, postal code and credit card
information. The Customer Id is thus connected to an end user’s account, and by extension can be used to find the user’s current:
Email address.
Hardware ID
All other data related to the end user in the iWin system.
If a user has multiple accounts within a single website or multiple websites operated by iWin, each account has a unique Customer ID.
ADVERTISING
Our Advertisers
IWin's advertisers and advertising vendors display targeted advertisements. Although we do not provide any personal information to the advertiser or
advertising vendor, by interacting with or clicking on an ad you acknowledge the possibility that the advertiser may assume you meet the targeting criteria
used.
In addition to cookies placed by iWin or its agents as described above, advertisers and advertising vendors that serve ads onto our Sites may use their own
cookies or other tracking technologies. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any such advertisers and vendors.
HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION
Uses of your Personal Information
IWin will use your information primarily to provide you with our products and services and to receive payment from you. In order to do this, we may
determine whether you meet the minimum system requirements to use our products. We may also ask you to participate in surveys about products, services,
news, and events; we may offer you product upgrades and games for you to purchase or access through a paid subscription service. You may opt out of some of
these uses.
IWin may also provide Personal Information to companies we engage as contractors or agents to perform services for us, such as maintaining software,
providing email marketing, or administering a sweepstakes or contest. Information will be shared with contractors only to the extent reasonably necessary
for them to perform these services on our behalf, and pursuant to confidentiality obligations. Members should note that iWin may change this Policy at any
time, and therefore iWin may in the future store some information for additional purposes not currently included in this policy.
Uses of Usage Information
Usage Information may be used by iWin to analyze Site and Application use in order to optimize the Site and the Applications and improve the user
experience.
iWin may use the information collected from your computer related to technical aspects of your connecting to a Site or Application in order to facilitate
the provision of software updates, product support, and other services to you (if any) related to the Sites and Applications, to verify compliance with the
terms of the applicable Site or Application, to improve our products or services or to provide Services or technologies to you.
iWin uses third-party tracking services to measure the effectiveness of our marketing and advertisements to prospective customers and customers who have
used our services. These services do not obtain or store any personally identifying information, but do record user activity at an anonymous level, such as
pages viewed, buttons clicked, Games Manager application and game installs, account registrations and subscriptions created. Third party services may
assign a unique user identification number for these events, but this will not be associated with any personal information provided to iWin by the
user.
GENERALLY
Where is the information held?
We are a global organization and the computer systems on which we collect, store, and use the information collected or received are based in the United
States and elsewhere. Your personal information may be transferred to , used, processed, or held by IWin in the United States and in other countries,
including both member and non-member countries of the European Union, and used for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.
Third-Party Disclosure of Personal Information
IWin does not use your Personal Information for the purposes incompatible with those listed above. Other than as provided in this Privacy Policy, iWin does
not provide your Personal information to third parties unless you specifically consent to provide such information to a third party. Sometimes, certain
indirectly identifiable information needs to be communicated with third-party vendors, for example, to process an order you have made. We may also disclose
Personal Information when legally compelled to do so. In other words, when the law requires it or when we have reason to believe that a disclosure is
necessary or appropriate to address potential or actual injury or interference with the rights, property, or operations or iWin, our users or others.
Finally, if we undergo a merger or acquisition, or sell or otherwise transfer substantially all the assets of iWin, or relating to any website that we own
or operate or any product or service that we offer, Personal Information may be transferred to our successor or assign.
Selected Notifications
Occasionally we may also use the information we collect to notify you about new services, products and special offers we think you will find valuable. We
will send you this type of communication only if we have received your permission to do so.
iWin collects and may use the following data for Marketing via Email or on Social Media Websites such as Facebook, Twitter or Instagram. This data may only
be used for advertising and marketing purposes by iWin, and is not provided to any third party data collection or marketing services.
Email Address
Subscription Status (ACTIVE, CANCELLED, EXPIRED, DELINQUENT, none)
Purchaser Status
Names of games purchased
Name of games played
Number of games played
Total Minutes played
Subscription Start date
Subscription Cancellation date
Subscription Expired date
Last Login Date
Last Purchase Date
Postal Code
Country Code
iWin uses Constant Contact, a third-party Email Service Provider, to send emails to customers who have opted in to receive email notifications about to our
products and services. Constant Contact provides iWin with the following information for each email address within each of our email marketing lists. A unique
user may appear in more than one email marketing list if the user has opted-in to such lists:
Email Marketing Status (Subscribed, Unsubscribed, Cleaned)
Member Activity Rating
OPTIN Time
OPTIN IP Address
CONFIRM IP Address
Latitude for the IP address of the CONFIRM_IP.
Longitude for the IP address of the CONFIRM_IP.
GMTOFF The number of hours to add or remove to UTC time to get to the time zone for that contact.
DSTOFF The number of hours to add or remove to UTC time to get to the contact's timezone, taking into account hours lost or gained due to daylight
savings time.
TIMEZONE/CITY
LAST_CHANGED The date and time when information in the contact's profile was last changed or updated.
LEID and EUID
LEID is the unique identifier for a contact, specific to a list.
EUID is the unique identifier for a contact on the account level, across all lists.
Member Activity Rating may be used in email marketing to target content or promotions to subscribers based on their history of activity opening or clicking
on emails from iWin.
IP addresses and timezones may be used in email marketing to target content and promotions to users in various geographic locations. Users who have opted-in
to receive notifications from iWin may unsubscribe at any time via a link in the footer of the email, or by contacting iWin Customer Support. Once the user
has unsubscribed from a list, the Email Marketing Status for the user will change to “Unsubscribed” and iWin will not contact the user again via that list.
Constant Contact will continue to store the user’s email address, personal information listed above and campaign activity in the list. If the user wishes for any
or all personal information to be removed from the list, the user may click on a link in the email’s footer to update their email subscription profile or
request this by contacting iWin Customer Support.
iWin understands that a user’s interest in our products and services may change over time. Once 12 months has passed since the last date a user has opened
an email from iWin or one of its partners, iWin will remove the user’s email address and personal data from the Constant Contact system. How Does IWin Protect Your
Information and Secure Information Transmissions?
We use industry standard technology and services to protect and secure your information. We will never initiate any email communication with you that
requests your private information beyond the purposes of user identification for support. In general, we request that you do not send private information
to us by email. Please contact iWin support if you have any questions or concerns.
Children's Online Privacy Protection
The safety of children is important to us. IWin's websites are for a general audience that is not directed to children under the age of 18. Similarly,
iWin's services are not directed to or intended for anyone under the age of 18. IWin will not knowingly accept members who are under the age of 18 years
nor will it knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from or about anyone under the age of 18 years. IWin relies on the
truthfulness of the registration when accepting new Members. In the event that iWin receives information that establishes that a Member is under the age of
18 years, iWin reserves the right, but not the obligation, to terminate that Member's membership or take other steps that it determines are appropriate in
the circumstances, such as providing parental notification. IWin may also delete all information in our databases about that terminated Member.
Employee Access, Training, and Expectations
Our corporate values, ethical standards, and practices are committed to the appropriate protection of customer and visitor information. In general, our
business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons,
processes, and transactions. This obligation continues once an employee has left our company.
What About Other Websites Linked to Our Website?
We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Sites or accessed through our Applications, nor the information or
content contained in any search results or third-party websites. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics
that may be of interest to the users of our Sites and Applications. Please remember that when you use a link to go from a Site to another website, our
Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link on one of our Sites, is
subject to that website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.
Your Consent
By using any of our Sites or Applications, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Modification of Privacy Policy by IWin
IWin reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice that we are changing this Privacy Policy. If there is a
change to this Privacy Policy, we will post the change on the Site or with the Application to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it,
and under what circumstances we may disclose it. You will be deemed to have accepted such change if you continue to use the Site or Application after the
new policy has been posted. In the event that this document conflicts in any way with the User Agreement, the User Agreement shall take precedence over the
relationship.
Effective: May 25, 2018
©2020 iWIn Inc. All Rights Reserved
About Us
Terms of Use
Support
Privacy Policy
Powered by
×
Sign In
The email address you entered is already in use. Please specify a different one or sign in as a returning user.
The email address you provided is not valid. Please enter a valid email address and try again.
Your password must be a minimum of 6 characters without spaces.
Your password must be a minimum of 6 characters and a maximum of 128 characters, without spaces.
Your password must be a minimum of 6 characters without spaces.
There was a problem when you tried to sign up. Please try again.
We are experiencing some technical issues, please try again in a few minutes.
The email address you entered is not valid. Please enter a valid email address and try again.
Continue with Facebook
This doesn't let the app post to Facebook
or
Create Your Account
Keep me signed in
By creating an account with www.arcadetown.com, you consent to iWin's collection, storage and use of your personal and usage information as outlined in the iWin Privacy Policy. If you have opted-in to receive email communication, you allow iWin to store and process data associated with your email activity in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
We noticed you were having problems signing in, you can reset your password by clicking Forgot Password.
We noticed you were having problems signing in, you can reset your password by clicking Forgot Password.
To protect your security, your account has been locked. Please check your email for instructions for unlocking your account or click Didn't receive unlock instructions
We are experiencing some technical issues, please try again in a few minutes.
Sign in with Facebook
This doesn't let the app post to Facebook
or
Show Password
Sign In
Keep me signed in
Forgot your email / password?
Forgot your password?
We have sent instructions on how to change your password to .
This email address is not associated with an account.
Please enter the email address associated with your account and we will send you instructions on how to reset your password.
Send Me Password Reset Instructions
Can't remember the email address you signed up with?Contact Customer Service
Create Your Account
Not you?
The email address you entered is already in use. Please specify a different one or sign in as a returning user.
The email address you provided is not valid. Please enter a valid email address and try again.
Your password must be a minimum of 6 characters without spaces.
Your password must be a minimum of 6 characters and a maximum of 128 characters, without spaces.
Your password must be a minimum of 6 characters without spaces.
There was a problem when you tried to sign up. Please try again.
We are experiencing some technical issues, please try again in a few minutes.
The email address you entered is not valid. Please enter a valid email address and try again.
Sign up with a different email
Show Password
Create Your Account
Keep me signed in
By creating an account with www.arcadetown.com, you consent to iWin's collection, storage and use of your personal and usage information as outlined in the iWin Privacy Policy. If you have opted-in to receive email communication, you allow iWin to store and process data associated with your email activity in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Resend Unlock ?
We have sent an email with instructions on how to unlock your account.
Your unlock instructions could not be sent at this time, please try again later.
Resend unlock instructions
×
×
Change Account Details
You have updated your account successfully.
There was a problem with your change attempt. Please try again.
The email address you provided is not valid. Please enter a valid email address and try again.
You must enter your current password in order to save any changes. Please try again.
The email address you have entered is already associated with an ArcadeTown account. Please select a different email address.
Your password must be a minimum of 6 characters without spaces.
Your password must be a minimum of 6 characters and a maximum of 128 characters, without spaces.
Your password must be a minimum of 6 characters without spaces.
Sorry, you cannot re-use a password that you have already used. Please try again.
Current Email:
New Email
(leave blank if you don't want to change it)
New Password (leave blank if you don't want to change it)
Show Passwords
To confirm these changes, please enter your password
Show Password
Cancel
Save Changes
OK
Please wait a moment
Please wait while the game starts
Please wait while we remove the game
×
Your queue is full
Please wait until your current game finishes downloading or you can cancel any of the following downloads and your game will be added to the queue.
Ok
×
YOUR FUTURE IS UNLIMITED
Unlimited access to over 250 games
No ads
First week free
Cancel anytime
Try Free for 7 Days
Confirmation Required
This action will take you to an older version of the iWin.com website and Games Manager, which supports accounts and subscriptions created before October 2017.
Before October 2017
After October 2017
If you prefer to stay on this version of the website, with the latest Games Manager, we do not recommend proceeding.
Would you like to proceed?
Click "Yes"
download-game-setup.exe
×
STEP 1
Click "Save File".
download-game-setup.exe
STEP 2
Click the Blue Arrow on the top right corner of your browser window to find your game download. Click on the game.
download-game-setup.exe
STEP 3
Click "Run"
download-game-setup.exe
×
STEP 1
Click "Run".
STEP 2
Click "Yes"
download-game-setup.exe
×
STEP 1
Click "Save".
STEP 2
Click "Run".
STEP 3
Click "Yes"
download-game-setup.exe
×
STEP 1
Click the file below
Arcadetown-Install...
STEP 2
Click "Yes"
Arcadetown-Install...
×
STEP 1
Click "Save File".
Arcadetown-Install...
STEP 2
Click the Blue Arrow on the top right corner of your browser window to find your game download. Click on the download.
Arcadetown-Install...
STEP 3
Click "Run"
Arcadetown-Install...
×
STEP 1
Click "Run".
STEP 2
Click "Yes"
Arcadetown-Install...
×
STEP 1
Click "Save".
STEP 2
Click "Run".
STEP 3
Click "Yes"
Arcadetown-Install...
